text,predicted_entities
"Earthquake tremors felt in Delhi, Gurugram and neighbouring areas, The earthquake struck 10km north of Haryanas Jhajjar, and it was measured to be of 3.7 magnitude, the National Centre for Seismology said. Delhi earthquake","[{'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Earthquake', 'start': 0, 'end': 10, 'score': np.float32(0.991)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi,', 'start': 27, 'end': 33, 'score': np.float32(0.972)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Gurugram', 'start': 34, 'end': 42, 'score': np.float32(0.975)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'neighbouring areas', 'start': 47, 'end': 65, 'score': np.float32(0.961)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquake', 'start': 71, 'end': 81, 'score': np.float32(0.997)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': '10km', 'start': 89, 'end': 93, 'score': np.float32(0.939)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Haryanas Jhajjar', 'start': 103, 'end': 119, 'score': np.float32(0.996)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': '3. 7 magnitude', 'start': 150, 'end': 163, 'score': np.float32(0.989)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'National Centre for', 'start': 169, 'end': 188, 'score': np.float32(0.952)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Seism', 'start': 189, 'end': 194, 'score': np.float32(0.515)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': '##ology', 'start': 194, 'end': 199, 'score': np.float32(0.494)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 206, 'end': 211, 'score': np.float32(0.964)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquake', 'start': 212, 'end': 222, 'score': np.float32(0.96)}]"
"earthquake A 6.7magnitude earthquake hit NorthEast India on Wednesday morning, as per the National Center for Seismology Earthquake Assam WestBengal 24topnews","[{'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquake', 'start': 0, 'end': 10, 'score': np.float32(0.989)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': '6. 7magnitude', 'start': 13, 'end': 25, 'score': np.float32(0.974)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquake', 'start': 26, 'end': 36, 'score': np.float32(0.996)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'North', 'start': 41, 'end': 46, 'score': np.float32(0.961)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': '##East', 'start': 46, 'end': 50, 'score': np.float32(0.745)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'India', 'start': 51, 'end': 56, 'score': np.float32(0.637)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'National Center for', 'start': 90, 'end': 109, 'score': np.float32(0.917)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Seismology', 'start': 110, 'end': 120, 'score': np.float32(0.605)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Earthquake', 'start': 121, 'end': 131, 'score': np.float32(0.891)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Assam', 'start': 132, 'end': 137, 'score': np.float32(0.677)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'WestB', 'start': 138, 'end': 143, 'score': np.float32(0.462)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##eng', 'start': 143, 'end': 146, 'score': np.float32(0.273)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': '##al', 'start': 146, 'end': 148, 'score': np.float32(0.749)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': '24topnews', 'start': 149, 'end': 158, 'score': np.float32(0.607)}]"
"Earthquake of magnitude 3.0 occurred at 06:09:41 IST, in WSW of Itanagar, Arunachal Pradesh: National Center for Seismology earthquake EarthMix EarthquakePH","[{'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Earthquake', 'start': 0, 'end': 10, 'score': np.float32(0.991)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': 'magnitude', 'start': 14, 'end': 23, 'score': np.float32(0.884)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': '3. 0', 'start': 24, 'end': 27, 'score': np.float32(0.865)}, {'entity': 'DATE_TIME', 'word': '06 : 09 : 41 IST', 'start': 40, 'end': 52, 'score': np.float32(0.961)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'WSW', 'start': 57, 'end': 60, 'score': np.float32(0.427)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Itanagar,', 'start': 64, 'end': 73, 'score': np.float32(0.961)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Arunachal Pradesh', 'start': 74, 'end': 91, 'score': np.float32(0.99)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'National Center for', 'start': 93, 'end': 112, 'score': np.float32(0.92)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Seismology', 'start': 113, 'end': 123, 'score': np.float32(0.526)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquake', 'start': 124, 'end': 134, 'score': np.float32(0.745)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'EarthMix', 'start': 135, 'end': 143, 'score': np.float32(0.875)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Earthquake', 'start': 144, 'end': 154, 'score': np.float32(0.941)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': '##PH', 'start': 154, 'end': 156, 'score': np.float32(0.873)}]"
Earthquake of magnitude 2.6 hits DelhiNCR DelhiEarthquake,"[{'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Earthquake', 'start': 0, 'end': 10, 'score': np.float32(0.993)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': 'magnitude 2. 6', 'start': 14, 'end': 27, 'score': np.float32(0.814)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'DelhiNCR', 'start': 33, 'end': 41, 'score': np.float32(0.865)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 42, 'end': 47, 'score': np.float32(0.973)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##Eart', 'start': 47, 'end': 51, 'score': np.float32(0.379)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': '##h', 'start': 51, 'end': 52, 'score': np.float32(0.767)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##quake', 'start': 52, 'end': 57, 'score': np.float32(0.929)}]"
Nepal       5.6    35 km    Delhi ncr       DelhiNCR earthquake earthquake earthquakenepal earthquakedelhi NepalEarthquake Earthquakes delhiearthquake viralvideo DelhiAirQuality DelhiPollution,"[{'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'Nepal', 'start': 0, 'end': 5, 'score': np.float32(0.636)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': '5. 6 35 km', 'start': 12, 'end': 24, 'score': np.float32(0.711)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 28, 'end': 33, 'score': np.float32(0.637)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': 'ncr', 'start': 34, 'end': 37, 'score': np.float32(0.466)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 44, 'end': 49, 'score': np.float32(0.576)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': '##NCR', 'start': 49, 'end': 52, 'score': np.float32(0.586)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquake', 'start': 53, 'end': 63, 'score': np.float32(0.967)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquake', 'start': 64, 'end': 74, 'score': np.float32(0.968)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquakenepal', 'start': 75, 'end': 90, 'score': np.float32(0.673)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquake', 'start': 91, 'end': 101, 'score': np.float32(0.888)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': '##delhi', 'start': 101, 'end': 106, 'score': np.float32(0.765)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Nepal', 'start': 107, 'end': 112, 'score': np.float32(0.404)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##Earthquake', 'start': 112, 'end': 122, 'score': np.float32(0.633)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Earthquakes', 'start': 123, 'end': 134, 'score': np.float32(0.944)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'delhi', 'start': 135, 'end': 140, 'score': np.float32(0.708)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##ear', 'start': 140, 'end': 143, 'score': np.float32(0.451)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': '##th', 'start': 143, 'end': 145, 'score': np.float32(0.49)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##quake', 'start': 145, 'end': 150, 'score': np.float32(0.895)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'viralvideo', 'start': 151, 'end': 161, 'score': np.float32(0.652)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'DelhiAirQuality', 'start': 162, 'end': 177, 'score': np.float32(0.801)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'DelhiPollution', 'start': 178, 'end': 192, 'score': np.float32(0.782)}]"
"   ,       ,      ? DelhiNCR delhiearthquake NepalEarthquake Nepal earthquake  ","[{'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': ',', 'start': 3, 'end': 4, 'score': np.float32(0.331)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': '?', 'start': 18, 'end': 19, 'score': np.float32(0.212)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 20, 'end': 25, 'score': np.float32(0.526)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': '##NCR', 'start': 25, 'end': 28, 'score': np.float32(0.537)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'delhiearth', 'start': 29, 'end': 39, 'score': np.float32(0.763)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##quake', 'start': 39, 'end': 44, 'score': np.float32(0.827)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Nepal', 'start': 45, 'end': 50, 'score': np.float32(0.554)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##Earthquake', 'start': 50, 'end': 60, 'score': np.float32(0.703)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'Nepal', 'start': 61, 'end': 66, 'score': np.float32(0.47)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquake', 'start': 67, 'end': 77, 'score': np.float32(0.519)}]"
Strong earthquake tremors felt in Delhi delhiearthquake bhukamp,"[{'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquake', 'start': 7, 'end': 17, 'score': np.float32(0.996)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi delhiearth', 'start': 34, 'end': 50, 'score': np.float32(0.738)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##quake', 'start': 50, 'end': 55, 'score': np.float32(0.714)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'bhukamp', 'start': 56, 'end': 63, 'score': np.float32(0.965)}]"
Strong tremors felt in Delhi. Hope yall are safe! DelhiEarthquake Earthquake,"[{'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 23, 'end': 28, 'score': np.float32(0.994)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##ll', 'start': 37, 'end': 39, 'score': np.float32(0.634)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 50, 'end': 55, 'score': np.float32(0.966)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##Earthquake', 'start': 55, 'end': 65, 'score': np.float32(0.646)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Earthquake', 'start': 66, 'end': 76, 'score': np.float32(0.968)}]"
"Magnitude 2.6 Earthquake Jolts Delhi, No Damage Reported  Earthquake Delhi BreakingNews DelhiEarthquake","[{'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Magnitude', 'start': 0, 'end': 9, 'score': np.float32(0.656)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': '2. 6', 'start': 10, 'end': 13, 'score': np.float32(0.737)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Earthquake Jolts', 'start': 14, 'end': 30, 'score': np.float32(0.881)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 31, 'end': 36, 'score': np.float32(0.676)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'No', 'start': 38, 'end': 40, 'score': np.float32(0.388)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Damage', 'start': 41, 'end': 47, 'score': np.float32(0.652)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Earthquake', 'start': 58, 'end': 68, 'score': np.float32(0.979)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 69, 'end': 74, 'score': np.float32(0.781)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'BreakingNews', 'start': 75, 'end': 87, 'score': np.float32(0.728)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 88, 'end': 93, 'score': np.float32(0.517)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': '##E', 'start': 93, 'end': 94, 'score': np.float32(0.46)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##arthquake', 'start': 94, 'end': 103, 'score': np.float32(0.51)}]"
"Nepal hit by fresh 5.6 magnitude earthquake, tremors felt across DelhiNCR DelhiNCR earthquakes  delhiearthquake DelhiNCREarthquake nepal earthquake NepalEarthquake","[{'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Nepal', 'start': 0, 'end': 5, 'score': np.float32(0.541)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': '5. 6 magnitude', 'start': 19, 'end': 32, 'score': np.float32(0.993)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquake', 'start': 33, 'end': 43, 'score': np.float32(0.992)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 65, 'end': 70, 'score': np.float32(0.971)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': '##NC', 'start': 70, 'end': 72, 'score': np.float32(0.566)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': '##R', 'start': 72, 'end': 73, 'score': np.float32(0.668)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 74, 'end': 79, 'score': np.float32(0.841)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': '##NCR', 'start': 79, 'end': 82, 'score': np.float32(0.602)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquakes', 'start': 83, 'end': 94, 'score': np.float32(0.926)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'delhiearthquake', 'start': 96, 'end': 111, 'score': np.float32(0.625)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 112, 'end': 117, 'score': np.float32(0.923)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': '##NC', 'start': 117, 'end': 119, 'score': np.float32(0.233)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': '##RE', 'start': 119, 'end': 121, 'score': np.float32(0.314)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##art', 'start': 121, 'end': 124, 'score': np.float32(0.266)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': '##h', 'start': 124, 'end': 125, 'score': np.float32(0.401)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##quake nepal', 'start': 125, 'end': 136, 'score': np.float32(0.74)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquake', 'start': 137, 'end': 147, 'score': np.float32(0.694)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Nepal', 'start': 148, 'end': 153, 'score': np.float32(0.807)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': '##E', 'start': 153, 'end': 154, 'score': np.float32(0.225)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##arthquake', 'start': 154, 'end': 163, 'score': np.float32(0.657)}]"
"Strong tremors felt in Delhi as 5.6magnitude earthquake hits Nepal, according to National Center for Seismology. DelhiNCR delhiearthquake DelhiQuake NepalEarthquake","[{'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 23, 'end': 28, 'score': np.float32(0.995)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': '5. 6magnitude', 'start': 32, 'end': 44, 'score': np.float32(0.961)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquake', 'start': 45, 'end': 55, 'score': np.float32(0.997)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Nepal', 'start': 61, 'end': 66, 'score': np.float32(0.988)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'National Center for', 'start': 81, 'end': 100, 'score': np.float32(0.956)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Seism', 'start': 101, 'end': 106, 'score': np.float32(0.484)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': '##ology', 'start': 106, 'end': 111, 'score': np.float32(0.508)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 113, 'end': 118, 'score': np.float32(0.525)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': '##NCR', 'start': 118, 'end': 121, 'score': np.float32(0.764)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'del', 'start': 122, 'end': 125, 'score': np.float32(0.55)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##hiearthquake', 'start': 125, 'end': 137, 'score': np.float32(0.758)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 138, 'end': 143, 'score': np.float32(0.742)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##Quake', 'start': 143, 'end': 148, 'score': np.float32(0.883)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Nepal', 'start': 149, 'end': 154, 'score': np.float32(0.727)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##Earthquake', 'start': 154, 'end': 164, 'score': np.float32(0.735)}]"
       Earthquake DelhiNCR   delhiearthquake,"[{'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Earthquake', 'start': 7, 'end': 17, 'score': np.float32(0.961)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'DelhiNCR', 'start': 18, 'end': 26, 'score': np.float32(0.788)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'delhi', 'start': 29, 'end': 34, 'score': np.float32(0.658)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##ear', 'start': 34, 'end': 37, 'score': np.float32(0.331)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': '##th', 'start': 37, 'end': 39, 'score': np.float32(0.779)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##quake', 'start': 39, 'end': 44, 'score': np.float32(0.779)}]"
"Earthquake Tremors felt in Northern India, Including DelhiNCR, on Monday Evening. According to the National Center for Seismology NCS, Nepal Struck by 5.6 Magnitude Earthquake. DelhiEarthquake earthquakedelhi NepalEarthquake Earthquake Nepal ABPLive","[{'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Earthquake', 'start': 0, 'end': 10, 'score': np.float32(0.987)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Northern India', 'start': 27, 'end': 41, 'score': np.float32(0.977)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'DelhiNCR', 'start': 53, 'end': 61, 'score': np.float32(0.929)}, {'entity': 'DATE_TIME', 'word': 'Evening', 'start': 73, 'end': 80, 'score': np.float32(0.829)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'National Center for Se', 'start': 99, 'end': 121, 'score': np.float32(0.815)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##ism', 'start': 121, 'end': 124, 'score': np.float32(0.579)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': '##ology', 'start': 124, 'end': 129, 'score': np.float32(0.663)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'NCS', 'start': 130, 'end': 133, 'score': np.float32(0.974)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Nepal', 'start': 135, 'end': 140, 'score': np.float32(0.692)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##ru', 'start': 143, 'end': 145, 'score': np.float32(0.408)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': '5. 6 Magnitude', 'start': 151, 'end': 164, 'score': np.float32(0.92)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Earthquake', 'start': 165, 'end': 175, 'score': np.float32(0.983)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 177, 'end': 182, 'score': np.float32(0.791)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##Earthquake', 'start': 182, 'end': 192, 'score': np.float32(0.71)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquakedelhi', 'start': 193, 'end': 208, 'score': np.float32(0.579)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Nepal', 'start': 209, 'end': 214, 'score': np.float32(0.545)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': '##E', 'start': 214, 'end': 215, 'score': np.float32(0.205)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##arthquake', 'start': 215, 'end': 224, 'score': np.float32(0.81)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Earthquake', 'start': 225, 'end': 235, 'score': np.float32(0.976)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'Nepal', 'start': 236, 'end': 241, 'score': np.float32(0.869)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'ABPLive', 'start': 242, 'end': 249, 'score': np.float32(0.942)}]"
BreakingNews          ... Earthquake DelhiEarthquake tremors DelhiNCR News18JKLH,"[{'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'BreakingNews.', 'start': 0, 'end': 23, 'score': np.float32(0.836)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': '.', 'start': 23, 'end': 24, 'score': np.float32(0.306)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Earthquake', 'start': 26, 'end': 36, 'score': np.float32(0.985)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 37, 'end': 42, 'score': np.float32(0.826)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': '##E', 'start': 42, 'end': 43, 'score': np.float32(0.284)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': '##arth', 'start': 43, 'end': 47, 'score': np.float32(0.765)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##quake', 'start': 47, 'end': 52, 'score': np.float32(0.81)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##ors', 'start': 57, 'end': 60, 'score': np.float32(0.577)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 61, 'end': 66, 'score': np.float32(0.561)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': '##NCR News', 'start': 66, 'end': 74, 'score': np.float32(0.865)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': '##18', 'start': 74, 'end': 76, 'score': np.float32(0.797)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': '##JKLH', 'start': 76, 'end': 80, 'score': np.float32(0.868)}]"
Vese earthquakes aaya hai lekin ye fan hath se hila rha hu taki sab ko pta chle jaldi jaldi bhar niklna hai delhiearthquake earthquake,"[{'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'V', 'start': 0, 'end': 1, 'score': np.float32(0.487)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##ese earthquakes aaya hai lekin ye fan hath se hila rha hu taki sab ko pta chle', 'start': 1, 'end': 79, 'score': np.float32(0.458)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'j', 'start': 80, 'end': 81, 'score': np.float32(0.536)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##aldi', 'start': 81, 'end': 85, 'score': np.float32(0.436)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'j', 'start': 86, 'end': 87, 'score': np.float32(0.516)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##aldi bhar ni', 'start': 87, 'end': 99, 'score': np.float32(0.455)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': '##k', 'start': 99, 'end': 100, 'score': np.float32(0.353)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##lna hai', 'start': 100, 'end': 107, 'score': np.float32(0.4)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'delhi', 'start': 108, 'end': 113, 'score': np.float32(0.597)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##ear', 'start': 113, 'end': 116, 'score': np.float32(0.413)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': '##th', 'start': 116, 'end': 118, 'score': np.float32(0.52)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##quake', 'start': 118, 'end': 123, 'score': np.float32(0.657)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquake', 'start': 124, 'end': 134, 'score': np.float32(0.413)}]"
It seems some foreign agency is placing some device 200300meters down and causing earthquake tremors Govt should investigate delhiearthquake Delhi,"[{'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'foreign agency', 'start': 14, 'end': 28, 'score': np.float32(0.773)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': '200300meters', 'start': 52, 'end': 64, 'score': np.float32(0.71)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquake', 'start': 82, 'end': 92, 'score': np.float32(0.995)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'delhiearthquake', 'start': 125, 'end': 140, 'score': np.float32(0.674)}]"
"NCR        ,        delhiearthquake noida gurugram gurgaon NCR Jagoindiajago Jijnews","[{'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'NCR,', 'start': 0, 'end': 12, 'score': np.float32(0.77)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'delhiearth', 'start': 20, 'end': 30, 'score': np.float32(0.915)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##quake', 'start': 30, 'end': 35, 'score': np.float32(0.478)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'noida gurugram gurgaon', 'start': 36, 'end': 58, 'score': np.float32(0.872)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'NCR', 'start': 59, 'end': 62, 'score': np.float32(0.961)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Jagoindiajago Jijnews', 'start': 63, 'end': 84, 'score': np.float32(0.945)}]"
"BREAKING  An earthquake of magnitude 2.6 struck DelhiNCR on Saturday, according to the National Centre for Seismology. There was no report of casualty or damage to property.","[{'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'BR', 'start': 0, 'end': 2, 'score': np.float32(0.472)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##EAKING', 'start': 2, 'end': 8, 'score': np.float32(0.647)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquake', 'start': 13, 'end': 23, 'score': np.float32(0.997)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': 'magnitude 2. 6', 'start': 27, 'end': 40, 'score': np.float32(0.833)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'DelhiNCR', 'start': 48, 'end': 56, 'score': np.float32(0.965)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'National Centre for', 'start': 87, 'end': 106, 'score': np.float32(0.915)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Seismology', 'start': 107, 'end': 117, 'score': np.float32(0.524)}]"
:          ...  4:24   ..  5.9  .. earthquakedelhi DelhiNCR delhiearthquake asiannews,"[{'entity': 'DATE_TIME', 'word': ':... 4 : 24.. 5. 9.', 'start': 0, 'end': 33, 'score': np.float32(0.783)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquake', 'start': 35, 'end': 45, 'score': np.float32(0.976)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': '##delhi', 'start': 45, 'end': 50, 'score': np.float32(0.502)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 51, 'end': 56, 'score': np.float32(0.562)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': '##NCR', 'start': 56, 'end': 59, 'score': np.float32(0.949)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'delhi', 'start': 60, 'end': 65, 'score': np.float32(0.597)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##ear', 'start': 65, 'end': 68, 'score': np.float32(0.383)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': '##th', 'start': 68, 'end': 70, 'score': np.float32(0.808)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##quake', 'start': 70, 'end': 75, 'score': np.float32(0.852)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'as', 'start': 76, 'end': 78, 'score': np.float32(0.749)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': '##ian', 'start': 78, 'end': 81, 'score': np.float32(0.586)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': '##news', 'start': 81, 'end': 85, 'score': np.float32(0.529)}]"
 2.6 magnitude Earthquake Tremor was felt at Delhi Today at 3.36 pm  delhiearthquake,"[{'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': '2. 6 magnitude', 'start': 1, 'end': 14, 'score': np.float32(0.938)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Earthquake', 'start': 15, 'end': 25, 'score': np.float32(0.986)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##rem', 'start': 27, 'end': 30, 'score': np.float32(0.674)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 45, 'end': 50, 'score': np.float32(0.921)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'Today', 'start': 51, 'end': 56, 'score': np.float32(0.767)}, {'entity': 'DATE_TIME', 'word': '3. 36 pm', 'start': 60, 'end': 67, 'score': np.float32(0.855)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'delhi', 'start': 69, 'end': 74, 'score': np.float32(0.718)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##ear', 'start': 74, 'end': 77, 'score': np.float32(0.515)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': '##th', 'start': 77, 'end': 79, 'score': np.float32(0.767)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##quake', 'start': 79, 'end': 84, 'score': np.float32(0.807)}]"
"     , 2.6  . Delhi delhiearthquake earthquakes InKhabar latestnews","[{'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': ',', 'start': 5, 'end': 6, 'score': np.float32(0.343)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': '2', 'start': 7, 'end': 8, 'score': np.float32(0.163)}, {'entity': 'DATE_TIME', 'word': '. 6', 'start': 8, 'end': 10, 'score': np.float32(0.692)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi delhi', 'start': 14, 'end': 25, 'score': np.float32(0.635)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##earthquake', 'start': 25, 'end': 35, 'score': np.float32(0.815)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquakes', 'start': 36, 'end': 47, 'score': np.float32(0.803)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'In', 'start': 48, 'end': 50, 'score': np.float32(0.978)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': '##Khabar', 'start': 50, 'end': 56, 'score': np.float32(0.793)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'latestnews', 'start': 57, 'end': 67, 'score': np.float32(0.466)}]"
"2 Earthquake Shakes DelhiNCR A magnitude 5.6 quake rattled DelhiNCR recently, a stark reminder of Earths restless energy. DelhiEarthquake NatureIsPowerful TrendingEarth","[{'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Earthquake Shake', 'start': 2, 'end': 18, 'score': np.float32(0.905)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'DelhiNCR', 'start': 20, 'end': 28, 'score': np.float32(0.647)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'magnitude', 'start': 31, 'end': 40, 'score': np.float32(0.609)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': '5. 6', 'start': 41, 'end': 44, 'score': np.float32(0.935)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'quake', 'start': 45, 'end': 50, 'score': np.float32(0.819)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'DelhiNCR', 'start': 59, 'end': 67, 'score': np.float32(0.631)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Earth', 'start': 98, 'end': 103, 'score': np.float32(0.663)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'energy', 'start': 114, 'end': 120, 'score': np.float32(0.691)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 122, 'end': 127, 'score': np.float32(0.754)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': '##E', 'start': 127, 'end': 128, 'score': np.float32(0.323)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##art', 'start': 128, 'end': 131, 'score': np.float32(0.521)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': '##h', 'start': 131, 'end': 132, 'score': np.float32(0.376)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##quake', 'start': 132, 'end': 137, 'score': np.float32(0.751)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'NatureIs', 'start': 138, 'end': 146, 'score': np.float32(0.471)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': '##Powerful', 'start': 146, 'end': 154, 'score': np.float32(0.437)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Trending', 'start': 155, 'end': 163, 'score': np.float32(0.377)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': '##E', 'start': 163, 'end': 164, 'score': np.float32(0.341)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##art', 'start': 164, 'end': 167, 'score': np.float32(0.267)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': '##h', 'start': 167, 'end': 168, 'score': np.float32(0.668)}]"
are you guys feel earthquake at 11:05 pm today delhi delhiearthquake earthquake,"[{'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquake', 'start': 18, 'end': 28, 'score': np.float32(0.986)}, {'entity': 'DATE_TIME', 'word': '11 : 05 pm', 'start': 32, 'end': 40, 'score': np.float32(0.963)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'delhi delhi', 'start': 47, 'end': 58, 'score': np.float32(0.929)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##ear', 'start': 58, 'end': 61, 'score': np.float32(0.234)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': '##th', 'start': 61, 'end': 63, 'score': np.float32(0.788)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##quake earthquake', 'start': 63, 'end': 79, 'score': np.float32(0.609)}]"
Another Earthquake tremors felt in DelhiNCR earthquakedelhi DelhiNCR delhiearthquake,"[{'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Earthquake', 'start': 8, 'end': 18, 'score': np.float32(0.986)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 35, 'end': 40, 'score': np.float32(0.961)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': '##NCR', 'start': 40, 'end': 43, 'score': np.float32(0.564)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquake', 'start': 44, 'end': 54, 'score': np.float32(0.972)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': '##delhi', 'start': 54, 'end': 59, 'score': np.float32(0.698)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 60, 'end': 65, 'score': np.float32(0.874)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': '##NCR', 'start': 65, 'end': 68, 'score': np.float32(0.539)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'delhi', 'start': 69, 'end': 74, 'score': np.float32(0.732)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##earthquake', 'start': 74, 'end': 84, 'score': np.float32(0.605)}]"
Strong earthquake tremors of Magnitude 5.6 felt in Delhi at 04:16 PM Lat: 28.89  Long: 82.36 Depth: 10 Km Region: Nepal the National Centre for Seismology DelhiNCR earthquakes  delhiearthquake DelhiNCREarthquake nepal earthquake NepalEarthquake,"[{'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquake', 'start': 7, 'end': 17, 'score': np.float32(0.997)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Magni', 'start': 29, 'end': 34, 'score': np.float32(0.46)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': '##tude', 'start': 34, 'end': 38, 'score': np.float32(0.521)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': '5. 6', 'start': 39, 'end': 42, 'score': np.float32(0.939)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 51, 'end': 56, 'score': np.float32(0.994)}, {'entity': 'DATE_TIME', 'word': '04 : 16 PM', 'start': 60, 'end': 68, 'score': np.float32(0.936)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'La', 'start': 69, 'end': 71, 'score': np.float32(0.2)}, {'entity': 'DATE_TIME', 'word': '##t : 28. 89', 'start': 71, 'end': 79, 'score': np.float32(0.691)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': 'Long', 'start': 81, 'end': 85, 'score': np.float32(0.477)}, {'entity': 'DATE_TIME', 'word': ':', 'start': 85, 'end': 86, 'score': np.float32(0.51)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': '82. 36 Depth', 'start': 87, 'end': 98, 'score': np.float32(0.548)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': ':', 'start': 98, 'end': 99, 'score': np.float32(0.239)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': '10 Km', 'start': 100, 'end': 105, 'score': np.float32(0.943)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Nepal', 'start': 114, 'end': 119, 'score': np.float32(0.716)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'National Centre for', 'start': 124, 'end': 143, 'score': np.float32(0.852)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Seismology', 'start': 144, 'end': 154, 'score': np.float32(0.486)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 155, 'end': 160, 'score': np.float32(0.528)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': '##NCR', 'start': 160, 'end': 163, 'score': np.float32(0.69)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquakes', 'start': 164, 'end': 175, 'score': np.float32(0.962)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'delhiearthquake', 'start': 177, 'end': 192, 'score': np.float32(0.736)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 193, 'end': 198, 'score': np.float32(0.805)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': '##NC', 'start': 198, 'end': 200, 'score': np.float32(0.237)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##REarthquake', 'start': 200, 'end': 211, 'score': np.float32(0.608)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'nepal', 'start': 212, 'end': 217, 'score': np.float32(0.721)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquake', 'start': 218, 'end': 228, 'score': np.float32(0.837)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Nepal', 'start': 229, 'end': 234, 'score': np.float32(0.655)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##Earthquake', 'start': 234, 'end': 244, 'score': np.float32(0.68)}]"
NCR             Delhi delhiearthquake earthquake,"[{'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'NCR', 'start': 0, 'end': 3, 'score': np.float32(0.974)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi delhi', 'start': 16, 'end': 27, 'score': np.float32(0.641)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##ear', 'start': 27, 'end': 30, 'score': np.float32(0.355)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': '##th', 'start': 30, 'end': 32, 'score': np.float32(0.763)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##quake', 'start': 32, 'end': 37, 'score': np.float32(0.762)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquake', 'start': 38, 'end': 48, 'score': np.float32(0.826)}]"
"BreakingNews :            2.6,     DelhiPolice Earthquake delhiearthquake earthquakedelhi","[{'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'BreakingNews', 'start': 0, 'end': 12, 'score': np.float32(0.896)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': '2.', 'start': 26, 'end': 28, 'score': np.float32(0.358)}, {'entity': 'DATE_TIME', 'word': '6', 'start': 28, 'end': 29, 'score': np.float32(0.432)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 35, 'end': 40, 'score': np.float32(0.737)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': '##Police', 'start': 40, 'end': 46, 'score': np.float32(0.708)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Earthquake', 'start': 47, 'end': 57, 'score': np.float32(0.924)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'del', 'start': 58, 'end': 61, 'score': np.float32(0.339)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': '##hi', 'start': 61, 'end': 63, 'score': np.float32(0.381)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##ear', 'start': 63, 'end': 66, 'score': np.float32(0.449)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': '##th', 'start': 66, 'end': 68, 'score': np.float32(0.545)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##quake', 'start': 68, 'end': 73, 'score': np.float32(0.876)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquakedel', 'start': 74, 'end': 87, 'score': np.float32(0.75)}]"
"Earthquake again in DelhiNCR Delhi ncr earthquakes earthquake earthquake earthquakenepal Nepal earthquakedelhi earthquakes Delhi NepalEarthquake Nepal Earthquakes DelhiNCR HeavyRain Israel delhiearthquake viralvideo DelhiAirQuality, DelhiPollution","[{'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Earthquake', 'start': 0, 'end': 10, 'score': np.float32(0.986)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 20, 'end': 25, 'score': np.float32(0.974)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': '##NCR', 'start': 25, 'end': 28, 'score': np.float32(0.686)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 29, 'end': 34, 'score': np.float32(0.87)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'n', 'start': 35, 'end': 36, 'score': np.float32(0.195)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##cr', 'start': 36, 'end': 38, 'score': np.float32(0.365)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquakes', 'start': 39, 'end': 50, 'score': np.float32(0.934)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquake', 'start': 51, 'end': 61, 'score': np.float32(0.959)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquake', 'start': 62, 'end': 72, 'score': np.float32(0.942)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquakenepal', 'start': 73, 'end': 88, 'score': np.float32(0.66)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Nepal', 'start': 89, 'end': 94, 'score': np.float32(0.528)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquake', 'start': 95, 'end': 105, 'score': np.float32(0.911)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': '##delhi', 'start': 105, 'end': 110, 'score': np.float32(0.626)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquakes', 'start': 111, 'end': 122, 'score': np.float32(0.886)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi Nepal', 'start': 123, 'end': 134, 'score': np.float32(0.709)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': '##E', 'start': 134, 'end': 135, 'score': np.float32(0.257)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##arthquake', 'start': 135, 'end': 144, 'score': np.float32(0.695)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'Nepal', 'start': 145, 'end': 150, 'score': np.float32(0.438)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Earthquakes', 'start': 151, 'end': 162, 'score': np.float32(0.937)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 163, 'end': 168, 'score': np.float32(0.518)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': '##NCR', 'start': 168, 'end': 171, 'score': np.float32(0.704)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'HeavyRain Israel', 'start': 172, 'end': 188, 'score': np.float32(0.7)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'delhi', 'start': 189, 'end': 194, 'score': np.float32(0.379)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##earthquake', 'start': 194, 'end': 204, 'score': np.float32(0.629)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'viralvideo', 'start': 205, 'end': 215, 'score': np.float32(0.681)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'DelhiAirQuality', 'start': 216, 'end': 231, 'score': np.float32(0.82)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': ',', 'start': 231, 'end': 232, 'score': np.float32(0.215)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 233, 'end': 238, 'score': np.float32(0.767)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': '##Pollution', 'start': 238, 'end': 247, 'score': np.float32(0.682)}]"
Delhi NCR         delhiearthquake earthquake DelhiNCR,"[{'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 0, 'end': 5, 'score': np.float32(0.812)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'NCR', 'start': 6, 'end': 9, 'score': np.float32(0.854)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'delhi', 'start': 18, 'end': 23, 'score': np.float32(0.618)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##ear', 'start': 23, 'end': 26, 'score': np.float32(0.372)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': '##th', 'start': 26, 'end': 28, 'score': np.float32(0.717)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##quake', 'start': 28, 'end': 33, 'score': np.float32(0.809)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquake', 'start': 34, 'end': 44, 'score': np.float32(0.608)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 45, 'end': 50, 'score': np.float32(0.807)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': '##NCR', 'start': 50, 'end': 53, 'score': np.float32(0.902)}]"
BreakingNews  Strong earthquake tremors felt in Delhi... Earthquake DelhiEarthquake tremors DelhiNCR News18JKLH,"[{'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'BreakingNews', 'start': 0, 'end': 12, 'score': np.float32(0.925)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquake', 'start': 21, 'end': 31, 'score': np.float32(0.997)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 48, 'end': 53, 'score': np.float32(0.995)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Earthquake', 'start': 57, 'end': 67, 'score': np.float32(0.988)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 68, 'end': 73, 'score': np.float32(0.933)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': '##E', 'start': 73, 'end': 74, 'score': np.float32(0.242)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##arthquake', 'start': 74, 'end': 83, 'score': np.float32(0.844)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 92, 'end': 97, 'score': np.float32(0.655)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': '##NCR News', 'start': 97, 'end': 105, 'score': np.float32(0.893)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': '##18', 'start': 105, 'end': 107, 'score': np.float32(0.764)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': '##JKLH', 'start': 107, 'end': 111, 'score': np.float32(0.88)}]"
 :                       earthquake delhiearthquake,"[{'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquake delhiearthquake', 'start': 25, 'end': 51, 'score': np.float32(0.582)}]"
"Tremors felt in DelhiNCR as another earthquake of magnitude 5.6 on Richter scale hit Nepal, epicentre for the quake 233km north of Ayodhya in UttarPradesh Read more details on:  Delhiearthquake NepalEarthquake","[{'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'DelhiNCR', 'start': 16, 'end': 24, 'score': np.float32(0.8)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquake', 'start': 36, 'end': 46, 'score': np.float32(0.996)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': 'magnitude', 'start': 50, 'end': 59, 'score': np.float32(0.909)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': '5. 6 on', 'start': 60, 'end': 66, 'score': np.float32(0.813)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Richter', 'start': 67, 'end': 74, 'score': np.float32(0.685)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': 'scale', 'start': 75, 'end': 80, 'score': np.float32(0.941)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Nepal', 'start': 85, 'end': 90, 'score': np.float32(0.99)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'quake', 'start': 110, 'end': 115, 'score': np.float32(0.963)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': '233km', 'start': 116, 'end': 121, 'score': np.float32(0.94)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Ayodhya', 'start': 131, 'end': 138, 'score': np.float32(0.998)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'UttarPradesh', 'start': 142, 'end': 154, 'score': np.float32(0.995)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 178, 'end': 183, 'score': np.float32(0.957)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##earthquake', 'start': 183, 'end': 193, 'score': np.float32(0.619)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Nepal', 'start': 194, 'end': 199, 'score': np.float32(0.9)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##Earthquake', 'start': 199, 'end': 209, 'score': np.float32(0.721)}]"
BREAKINGNEWS       earthquakes DelhiNCR delhiearthquake Delhi earthquake earthquakes,"[{'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'BR', 'start': 0, 'end': 2, 'score': np.float32(0.219)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##EAKINGNEWS', 'start': 2, 'end': 12, 'score': np.float32(0.618)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquakes', 'start': 19, 'end': 30, 'score': np.float32(0.938)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'DelhiNCR', 'start': 31, 'end': 39, 'score': np.float32(0.738)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'delhi', 'start': 40, 'end': 45, 'score': np.float32(0.505)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##ear', 'start': 45, 'end': 48, 'score': np.float32(0.383)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': '##th', 'start': 48, 'end': 50, 'score': np.float32(0.556)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##quake', 'start': 50, 'end': 55, 'score': np.float32(0.701)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 56, 'end': 61, 'score': np.float32(0.933)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquake', 'start': 62, 'end': 72, 'score': np.float32(0.881)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquakes', 'start': 73, 'end': 84, 'score': np.float32(0.911)}]"
"BreakingNews: Earthquake Tremors Felt in Delhi, Neighbouring Areas Earthquake DelhiEarthquake Tremors Delhi  ","[{'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'BreakingNews', 'start': 0, 'end': 12, 'score': np.float32(0.854)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Earthquake Tremors Felt', 'start': 14, 'end': 37, 'score': np.float32(0.811)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 41, 'end': 46, 'score': np.float32(0.981)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##eighbouring Areas', 'start': 49, 'end': 66, 'score': np.float32(0.346)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Earthquake', 'start': 67, 'end': 77, 'score': np.float32(0.974)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 78, 'end': 83, 'score': np.float32(0.907)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##Earthquake Tremors', 'start': 83, 'end': 101, 'score': np.float32(0.594)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 102, 'end': 107, 'score': np.float32(0.426)}]"
"Earthquake of Magnitude:5.6, Occurred on 06112023, 16:16:40 IST, Lat: 28.89  Long: 82.36, Depth: 10 Km ,Region: Nepal Tremores feels in parts of north india earthquakes DelhiNCR delhiearthquake Delhi earthquake","[{'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Earthquake', 'start': 0, 'end': 10, 'score': np.float32(0.989)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Magnitude', 'start': 14, 'end': 23, 'score': np.float32(0.403)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': '5. 6', 'start': 24, 'end': 27, 'score': np.float32(0.916)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##ccur', 'start': 30, 'end': 34, 'score': np.float32(0.409)}, {'entity': 'DATE_TIME', 'word': '06112023, 16 : 16 : 40 IST', 'start': 41, 'end': 63, 'score': np.float32(0.933)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Lat', 'start': 65, 'end': 68, 'score': np.float32(0.61)}, {'entity': 'DATE_TIME', 'word': ': 28. 89', 'start': 68, 'end': 75, 'score': np.float32(0.739)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': 'Long', 'start': 77, 'end': 81, 'score': np.float32(0.503)}, {'entity': 'DATE_TIME', 'word': ':', 'start': 81, 'end': 82, 'score': np.float32(0.381)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': '82. 36,', 'start': 83, 'end': 89, 'score': np.float32(0.63)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'De', 'start': 90, 'end': 92, 'score': np.float32(0.303)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': '##pth', 'start': 92, 'end': 95, 'score': np.float32(0.301)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': ':', 'start': 95, 'end': 96, 'score': np.float32(0.219)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': '10 Km', 'start': 97, 'end': 102, 'score': np.float32(0.932)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': 'Region', 'start': 104, 'end': 110, 'score': np.float32(0.173)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': ':', 'start': 110, 'end': 111, 'score': np.float32(0.15)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Nepal', 'start': 112, 'end': 117, 'score': np.float32(0.718)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Tremores', 'start': 118, 'end': 126, 'score': np.float32(0.685)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'north', 'start': 145, 'end': 150, 'score': np.float32(0.861)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'india', 'start': 151, 'end': 156, 'score': np.float32(0.802)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquakes', 'start': 157, 'end': 168, 'score': np.float32(0.986)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 169, 'end': 174, 'score': np.float32(0.484)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': '##NCR', 'start': 174, 'end': 177, 'score': np.float32(0.762)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'del', 'start': 178, 'end': 181, 'score': np.float32(0.523)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': '##hi', 'start': 181, 'end': 183, 'score': np.float32(0.391)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##earthquake', 'start': 183, 'end': 193, 'score': np.float32(0.786)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 194, 'end': 199, 'score': np.float32(0.934)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquake', 'start': 200, 'end': 210, 'score': np.float32(0.881)}]"
"Another earthquake has occurred in Indias capital, Delhi, with a magnitude of 2.6. Many people have reported feeling the tremors. Depth: 10 Km ,Location: North District,Delhi DelhiQuake DelhiEarthquake IcelandEarthquakes earthquakes","[{'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquake', 'start': 8, 'end': 18, 'score': np.float32(0.997)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Indias capital', 'start': 35, 'end': 49, 'score': np.float32(0.977)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 51, 'end': 56, 'score': np.float32(0.927)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': 'magnitude', 'start': 65, 'end': 74, 'score': np.float32(0.749)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': '2. 6', 'start': 78, 'end': 81, 'score': np.float32(0.929)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': '##pt', 'start': 132, 'end': 134, 'score': np.float32(0.181)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##h', 'start': 134, 'end': 135, 'score': np.float32(0.435)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': '10 Km', 'start': 137, 'end': 142, 'score': np.float32(0.93)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'North District,', 'start': 154, 'end': 169, 'score': np.float32(0.737)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 169, 'end': 174, 'score': np.float32(0.598)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 175, 'end': 180, 'score': np.float32(0.908)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##Quake', 'start': 180, 'end': 185, 'score': np.float32(0.904)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 186, 'end': 191, 'score': np.float32(0.85)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##Earthquake', 'start': 191, 'end': 201, 'score': np.float32(0.812)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'IcelandEarthquakes', 'start': 202, 'end': 220, 'score': np.float32(0.751)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquakes', 'start': 221, 'end': 232, 'score': np.float32(0.823)}]"
NCR                           4  18      BreakingNews Earthquake DelhiNCR DelhiEarthquake BharatUpdate,"[{'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'NCR', 'start': 0, 'end': 3, 'score': np.float32(0.934)}, {'entity': 'DATE_TIME', 'word': '4 18', 'start': 30, 'end': 35, 'score': np.float32(0.587)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'BreakingNews', 'start': 41, 'end': 53, 'score': np.float32(0.704)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Earthquake', 'start': 54, 'end': 64, 'score': np.float32(0.964)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 65, 'end': 70, 'score': np.float32(0.862)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': '##NC', 'start': 70, 'end': 72, 'score': np.float32(0.526)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': '##R', 'start': 72, 'end': 73, 'score': np.float32(0.657)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 74, 'end': 79, 'score': np.float32(0.609)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': '##E', 'start': 79, 'end': 80, 'score': np.float32(0.343)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##art', 'start': 80, 'end': 83, 'score': np.float32(0.262)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': '##h', 'start': 83, 'end': 84, 'score': np.float32(0.909)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##quake', 'start': 84, 'end': 89, 'score': np.float32(0.711)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Bharat', 'start': 90, 'end': 96, 'score': np.float32(0.868)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': '##Update', 'start': 96, 'end': 102, 'score': np.float32(0.679)}]"
"Earthquake In Delhi:        ,       Earthquake EarthquakeInDelhi DelhiEarthquake Diwali","[{'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Earthquake In', 'start': 0, 'end': 13, 'score': np.float32(0.779)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 14, 'end': 19, 'score': np.float32(0.539)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Earthquake', 'start': 36, 'end': 46, 'score': np.float32(0.946)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Earthquake', 'start': 47, 'end': 57, 'score': np.float32(0.943)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': '##InD', 'start': 57, 'end': 60, 'score': np.float32(0.492)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': '##elhi Delhi', 'start': 60, 'end': 70, 'score': np.float32(0.642)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##Eart', 'start': 70, 'end': 74, 'score': np.float32(0.265)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': '##h', 'start': 74, 'end': 75, 'score': np.float32(0.718)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##quake', 'start': 75, 'end': 80, 'score': np.float32(0.752)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Diwali', 'start': 81, 'end': 87, 'score': np.float32(0.856)}]"
"     , 2.6     7         Earthquake NorthDelhi","[{'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': '2. 6 7', 'start': 7, 'end': 16, 'score': np.float32(0.609)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Earthquake', 'start': 25, 'end': 35, 'score': np.float32(0.969)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'NorthD', 'start': 36, 'end': 42, 'score': np.float32(0.461)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': '##elhi', 'start': 42, 'end': 46, 'score': np.float32(0.764)}]"
"DelhiNCREarthquake of Magnitude:5.6, Occurred on 06112023, 16:16:40 IST, Lat: 28.89  Long: 82.36, Depth: 10 Km ,Region: Nepal Tremores feels in parts of north india earthquakes DelhiNCR delhiearthquake RashmikaMandanna srilankacricketboard India","[{'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'DelhiNCRE', 'start': 0, 'end': 9, 'score': np.float32(0.754)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##arthquake', 'start': 9, 'end': 18, 'score': np.float32(0.81)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Magni', 'start': 22, 'end': 27, 'score': np.float32(0.395)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': '##tude', 'start': 27, 'end': 31, 'score': np.float32(0.445)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': '5. 6', 'start': 32, 'end': 35, 'score': np.float32(0.905)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##ccur', 'start': 38, 'end': 42, 'score': np.float32(0.427)}, {'entity': 'DATE_TIME', 'word': '06112023, 16 : 16 : 40 IST', 'start': 49, 'end': 71, 'score': np.float32(0.941)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Lat', 'start': 73, 'end': 76, 'score': np.float32(0.669)}, {'entity': 'DATE_TIME', 'word': ': 28. 89', 'start': 76, 'end': 83, 'score': np.float32(0.818)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': 'Long', 'start': 85, 'end': 89, 'score': np.float32(0.57)}, {'entity': 'DATE_TIME', 'word': ':', 'start': 89, 'end': 90, 'score': np.float32(0.438)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': '82. 36, Depth', 'start': 91, 'end': 103, 'score': np.float32(0.495)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': ':', 'start': 103, 'end': 104, 'score': np.float32(0.236)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': '10 Km', 'start': 105, 'end': 110, 'score': np.float32(0.926)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': 'Region', 'start': 112, 'end': 118, 'score': np.float32(0.162)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': ':', 'start': 118, 'end': 119, 'score': np.float32(0.147)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Nepal', 'start': 120, 'end': 125, 'score': np.float32(0.671)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Tremores', 'start': 126, 'end': 134, 'score': np.float32(0.814)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'north', 'start': 153, 'end': 158, 'score': np.float32(0.757)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'india', 'start': 159, 'end': 164, 'score': np.float32(0.753)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquakes', 'start': 165, 'end': 176, 'score': np.float32(0.979)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'DelhiNCR', 'start': 177, 'end': 185, 'score': np.float32(0.774)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'delhiearthquake', 'start': 186, 'end': 201, 'score': np.float32(0.808)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Rashmika', 'start': 202, 'end': 210, 'score': np.float32(0.942)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##M', 'start': 210, 'end': 211, 'score': np.float32(0.365)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': '##andanna', 'start': 211, 'end': 218, 'score': np.float32(0.881)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'srilankacricketboard', 'start': 219, 'end': 239, 'score': np.float32(0.56)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'India', 'start': 240, 'end': 245, 'score': np.float32(0.581)}]"
"Delhi NCR         delhiearthquake earthquake DelhiNCR DelhiNCR ,,ViratKohli India","[{'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 0, 'end': 5, 'score': np.float32(0.898)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'NCR', 'start': 6, 'end': 9, 'score': np.float32(0.854)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'del', 'start': 18, 'end': 21, 'score': np.float32(0.358)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': '##hi', 'start': 21, 'end': 23, 'score': np.float32(0.53)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##earthquake', 'start': 23, 'end': 33, 'score': np.float32(0.738)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquake', 'start': 34, 'end': 44, 'score': np.float32(0.69)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 45, 'end': 50, 'score': np.float32(0.587)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': '##NCR', 'start': 50, 'end': 53, 'score': np.float32(0.724)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'DelhiNCR,', 'start': 54, 'end': 64, 'score': np.float32(0.557)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'ViratKohli India', 'start': 65, 'end': 81, 'score': np.float32(0.924)}]"
"Strong earthquake of magnitude 5.7 struck Nepal tremors also felt in northern India and its adjoining areas. , Including Delhi NCR people rush out of their houses. the epicenter was 2km deep in jajarkot district of Nepal. earthquake NepalEarthquake DelhiNCR delhiearthquake","[{'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquake', 'start': 7, 'end': 17, 'score': np.float32(0.996)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': 'magnitude 5. 7', 'start': 21, 'end': 34, 'score': np.float32(0.865)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Nepal', 'start': 42, 'end': 47, 'score': np.float32(0.979)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'India', 'start': 78, 'end': 83, 'score': np.float32(0.526)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'its adjoining areas', 'start': 88, 'end': 107, 'score': np.float32(0.935)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 121, 'end': 126, 'score': np.float32(0.549)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'NCR', 'start': 127, 'end': 130, 'score': np.float32(0.839)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'houses', 'start': 156, 'end': 162, 'score': np.float32(0.421)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'epicenter', 'start': 168, 'end': 177, 'score': np.float32(0.711)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': '2km deep', 'start': 182, 'end': 190, 'score': np.float32(0.852)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'jajarkot district', 'start': 194, 'end': 211, 'score': np.float32(0.995)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Nepal', 'start': 215, 'end': 220, 'score': np.float32(0.979)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquake', 'start': 222, 'end': 232, 'score': np.float32(0.981)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Nepal', 'start': 233, 'end': 238, 'score': np.float32(0.552)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##Earthquake', 'start': 238, 'end': 248, 'score': np.float32(0.727)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 249, 'end': 254, 'score': np.float32(0.607)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': '##NCR', 'start': 254, 'end': 257, 'score': np.float32(0.934)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'delhi', 'start': 258, 'end': 263, 'score': np.float32(0.79)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##ear', 'start': 263, 'end': 266, 'score': np.float32(0.621)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': '##th', 'start': 266, 'end': 268, 'score': np.float32(0.621)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##quake', 'start': 268, 'end': 273, 'score': np.float32(0.766)}]"
Two earthquakes in 3 days: Are these warning bells of mega Himalayan quake? earthquake delhiearthquake,"[{'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquakes', 'start': 4, 'end': 15, 'score': np.float32(0.996)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': '3', 'start': 19, 'end': 20, 'score': np.float32(0.274)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'mega', 'start': 54, 'end': 58, 'score': np.float32(0.594)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Himalaya', 'start': 59, 'end': 67, 'score': np.float32(0.884)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##n', 'start': 67, 'end': 68, 'score': np.float32(0.661)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'quake', 'start': 69, 'end': 74, 'score': np.float32(0.942)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquake del', 'start': 76, 'end': 90, 'score': np.float32(0.687)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': '##hi', 'start': 90, 'end': 92, 'score': np.float32(0.288)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##ear', 'start': 92, 'end': 95, 'score': np.float32(0.514)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': '##th', 'start': 95, 'end': 97, 'score': np.float32(0.651)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##quake', 'start': 97, 'end': 102, 'score': np.float32(0.773)}]"
"Strong mag. 5.3 earthquake  38 km east of Dailekh, Karnali Pradesh, Nepal, on Monday, Nov 6, 2023 at 4:16 pm GMT 5:30 Earthquake Nepal Delhi Dailekh DelhiEarthquake","[{'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'mag', 'start': 7, 'end': 10, 'score': np.float32(0.512)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': '5. 3', 'start': 12, 'end': 15, 'score': np.float32(0.818)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquake', 'start': 16, 'end': 26, 'score': np.float32(0.988)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': '38 km', 'start': 28, 'end': 33, 'score': np.float32(0.888)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Dailekh', 'start': 42, 'end': 49, 'score': np.float32(0.993)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Karnali Pradesh, Nepal', 'start': 51, 'end': 73, 'score': np.float32(0.891)}, {'entity': 'DATE_TIME', 'word': 'Monday, Nov', 'start': 78, 'end': 89, 'score': np.float32(0.878)}, {'entity': 'DATE_TIME', 'word': '6, 2023', 'start': 90, 'end': 97, 'score': np.float32(0.887)}, {'entity': 'DATE_TIME', 'word': '4 : 16 pm GMT 5 : 30', 'start': 101, 'end': 117, 'score': np.float32(0.926)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Earthquake', 'start': 118, 'end': 128, 'score': np.float32(0.981)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Nepal Delhi', 'start': 129, 'end': 140, 'score': np.float32(0.639)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Dailekh Delhi', 'start': 141, 'end': 154, 'score': np.float32(0.911)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##Earthquake', 'start': 154, 'end': 164, 'score': np.float32(0.739)}]"
"    ,            DelhiEarthquake Earthquake","[{'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 17, 'end': 22, 'score': np.float32(0.842)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##Earthquake', 'start': 22, 'end': 32, 'score': np.float32(0.735)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Earthquake', 'start': 33, 'end': 43, 'score': np.float32(0.963)}]"
Again earthquake strikes Nepal with a magnitude of around 5.25.6 on Richter scale. Strong tremors felt in Delhi NCR region  other parts of northern India. earthquakes DelhiNCR NepalEarthquake earthquakedelhi delhiearthquake DelhiAirPollution Delhi   ,"[{'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquake', 'start': 6, 'end': 16, 'score': np.float32(0.998)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Nepal', 'start': 25, 'end': 30, 'score': np.float32(0.992)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': 'magnitude', 'start': 38, 'end': 47, 'score': np.float32(0.746)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': '5. 25. 6', 'start': 58, 'end': 64, 'score': np.float32(0.972)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Richter', 'start': 68, 'end': 75, 'score': np.float32(0.691)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': 'scale', 'start': 76, 'end': 81, 'score': np.float32(0.909)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi NCR region', 'start': 106, 'end': 122, 'score': np.float32(0.967)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'parts', 'start': 130, 'end': 135, 'score': np.float32(0.781)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'northern India', 'start': 139, 'end': 153, 'score': np.float32(0.819)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquakes', 'start': 155, 'end': 166, 'score': np.float32(0.986)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 167, 'end': 172, 'score': np.float32(0.778)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': '##NCR', 'start': 172, 'end': 175, 'score': np.float32(0.702)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Nepal', 'start': 176, 'end': 181, 'score': np.float32(0.658)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': '##E', 'start': 181, 'end': 182, 'score': np.float32(0.236)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##art', 'start': 182, 'end': 185, 'score': np.float32(0.473)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': '##h', 'start': 185, 'end': 186, 'score': np.float32(0.517)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##quake', 'start': 186, 'end': 191, 'score': np.float32(0.831)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquake', 'start': 192, 'end': 202, 'score': np.float32(0.954)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': '##delhi', 'start': 202, 'end': 207, 'score': np.float32(0.795)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'delhi', 'start': 208, 'end': 213, 'score': np.float32(0.797)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##ear', 'start': 213, 'end': 216, 'score': np.float32(0.57)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': '##th', 'start': 216, 'end': 218, 'score': np.float32(0.44)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##quake', 'start': 218, 'end': 223, 'score': np.float32(0.857)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'DelhiAirPollution', 'start': 224, 'end': 241, 'score': np.float32(0.819)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 242, 'end': 247, 'score': np.float32(0.669)}]"
Nepal  India  Again earthquake strikes Nepal with a magnitude of around 5.25.6 on Richter scale This is the second earthquake in past few days Strong tremors felt in Delhi NCR region  other parts of northern India NepalEarthquake Earthquake DelhiNCR DelhiEarthquake,"[{'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Nepal India', 'start': 0, 'end': 12, 'score': np.float32(0.806)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquake', 'start': 20, 'end': 30, 'score': np.float32(0.996)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Nepal', 'start': 39, 'end': 44, 'score': np.float32(0.993)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': 'magnitude', 'start': 52, 'end': 61, 'score': np.float32(0.715)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': '5. 25. 6 on', 'start': 72, 'end': 81, 'score': np.float32(0.937)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Richter', 'start': 82, 'end': 89, 'score': np.float32(0.5)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': 'scale', 'start': 90, 'end': 95, 'score': np.float32(0.914)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquake', 'start': 115, 'end': 125, 'score': np.float32(0.996)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi NCR region', 'start': 166, 'end': 182, 'score': np.float32(0.938)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'parts of', 'start': 190, 'end': 198, 'score': np.float32(0.599)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'northern India', 'start': 199, 'end': 213, 'score': np.float32(0.72)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Nepal', 'start': 214, 'end': 219, 'score': np.float32(0.907)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##Earthquake', 'start': 219, 'end': 229, 'score': np.float32(0.74)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Earthquake', 'start': 230, 'end': 240, 'score': np.float32(0.977)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 241, 'end': 246, 'score': np.float32(0.873)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': '##NC', 'start': 246, 'end': 248, 'score': np.float32(0.415)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': '##R', 'start': 248, 'end': 249, 'score': np.float32(0.677)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 250, 'end': 255, 'score': np.float32(0.757)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': '##E', 'start': 255, 'end': 256, 'score': np.float32(0.218)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##arthquake', 'start': 256, 'end': 265, 'score': np.float32(0.784)}]"
Strong earthquake tremors felt in Delhi earthquakes bhukamp ,"[{'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquake', 'start': 7, 'end': 17, 'score': np.float32(0.996)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 34, 'end': 39, 'score': np.float32(0.995)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'bhukamp', 'start': 52, 'end': 59, 'score': np.float32(0.955)}]"
"Earthquake of Magnitude:5.6, Occurred on 06112023, 16:16:40 IST, Lat: 28.89  Long: 82.36, Depth: 10 Km ,Region: Nepal Tremores feels in parts of north india earthquakes DelhiNCR delhiearthquake Delhi earthquake","[{'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Earthquake', 'start': 0, 'end': 10, 'score': np.float32(0.989)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Magnitude', 'start': 14, 'end': 23, 'score': np.float32(0.403)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': '5. 6', 'start': 24, 'end': 27, 'score': np.float32(0.916)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##ccur', 'start': 30, 'end': 34, 'score': np.float32(0.409)}, {'entity': 'DATE_TIME', 'word': '06112023, 16 : 16 : 40 IST', 'start': 41, 'end': 63, 'score': np.float32(0.933)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Lat', 'start': 65, 'end': 68, 'score': np.float32(0.61)}, {'entity': 'DATE_TIME', 'word': ': 28. 89', 'start': 68, 'end': 75, 'score': np.float32(0.739)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': 'Long', 'start': 77, 'end': 81, 'score': np.float32(0.503)}, {'entity': 'DATE_TIME', 'word': ':', 'start': 81, 'end': 82, 'score': np.float32(0.381)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': '82. 36,', 'start': 83, 'end': 89, 'score': np.float32(0.63)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'De', 'start': 90, 'end': 92, 'score': np.float32(0.303)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': '##pth', 'start': 92, 'end': 95, 'score': np.float32(0.301)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': ':', 'start': 95, 'end': 96, 'score': np.float32(0.219)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': '10 Km', 'start': 97, 'end': 102, 'score': np.float32(0.932)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': 'Region', 'start': 104, 'end': 110, 'score': np.float32(0.173)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': ':', 'start': 110, 'end': 111, 'score': np.float32(0.15)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Nepal', 'start': 112, 'end': 117, 'score': np.float32(0.718)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Tremores', 'start': 118, 'end': 126, 'score': np.float32(0.685)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'north', 'start': 145, 'end': 150, 'score': np.float32(0.861)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'india', 'start': 151, 'end': 156, 'score': np.float32(0.802)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquakes', 'start': 157, 'end': 168, 'score': np.float32(0.986)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 169, 'end': 174, 'score': np.float32(0.484)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': '##NCR', 'start': 174, 'end': 177, 'score': np.float32(0.762)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'del', 'start': 178, 'end': 181, 'score': np.float32(0.523)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': '##hi', 'start': 181, 'end': 183, 'score': np.float32(0.391)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##earthquake', 'start': 183, 'end': 193, 'score': np.float32(0.786)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 194, 'end': 199, 'score': np.float32(0.934)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquake', 'start': 200, 'end': 210, 'score': np.float32(0.881)}]"
BreakingNews :            2.6     Delhi Earthquake delhiearthquake earthquakedelhi,"[{'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'BreakingNews', 'start': 0, 'end': 12, 'score': np.float32(0.859)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': '2. 6', 'start': 26, 'end': 29, 'score': np.float32(0.629)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 34, 'end': 39, 'score': np.float32(0.447)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Earthquake', 'start': 40, 'end': 50, 'score': np.float32(0.92)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'delhi', 'start': 51, 'end': 56, 'score': np.float32(0.579)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##ear', 'start': 56, 'end': 59, 'score': np.float32(0.362)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': '##th', 'start': 59, 'end': 61, 'score': np.float32(0.733)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##quake', 'start': 61, 'end': 66, 'score': np.float32(0.835)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquakedel', 'start': 67, 'end': 80, 'score': np.float32(0.619)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': '##hi', 'start': 80, 'end': 82, 'score': np.float32(0.365)}]"
"NewsAlert DelhiNCR felt strong earthquake tremors on November 6, just days after a a 6.4 jolt. More details  Earthquake DelhiNCR DelhiEarthquake","[{'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'NewsAlert', 'start': 0, 'end': 9, 'score': np.float32(0.973)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 10, 'end': 15, 'score': np.float32(0.904)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': '##NCR', 'start': 15, 'end': 18, 'score': np.float32(0.832)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquake', 'start': 31, 'end': 41, 'score': np.float32(0.998)}, {'entity': 'DATE_TIME', 'word': 'November 6', 'start': 53, 'end': 63, 'score': np.float32(0.897)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': '6. 4 jolt', 'start': 85, 'end': 93, 'score': np.float32(0.968)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Earthquake', 'start': 109, 'end': 119, 'score': np.float32(0.981)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'DelhiNCR', 'start': 120, 'end': 128, 'score': np.float32(0.726)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'DelhiE', 'start': 129, 'end': 135, 'score': np.float32(0.482)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##arthquake', 'start': 135, 'end': 144, 'score': np.float32(0.734)}]"
    NCR        ...    5.6    .. earthquakes DelhiNCR delhiearthquake,"[{'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'NCR', 'start': 4, 'end': 7, 'score': np.float32(0.974)}, {'entity': 'DATE_TIME', 'word': '..', 'start': 15, 'end': 17, 'score': np.float32(0.24)}, {'entity': 'DATE_TIME', 'word': '5. 6', 'start': 22, 'end': 25, 'score': np.float32(0.596)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': '..', 'start': 29, 'end': 31, 'score': np.float32(0.663)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquakes', 'start': 32, 'end': 43, 'score': np.float32(0.938)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 44, 'end': 49, 'score': np.float32(0.523)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': '##NCR', 'start': 49, 'end': 52, 'score': np.float32(0.861)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'delhi', 'start': 53, 'end': 58, 'score': np.float32(0.758)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##ear', 'start': 58, 'end': 61, 'score': np.float32(0.365)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': '##th', 'start': 61, 'end': 63, 'score': np.float32(0.844)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##quake', 'start': 63, 'end': 68, 'score': np.float32(0.871)}]"
"Earthquake of Magnitude:5.6, Occurred on 06112023, 16:16:40 IST, Lat: 28.89  Long: 82.36, Depth: 10 Km ,Region: Nepal Tremores feels in parts of north india earthquakes DelhiNCR delhiearthquake","[{'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Earthquake', 'start': 0, 'end': 10, 'score': np.float32(0.989)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Magnitude', 'start': 14, 'end': 23, 'score': np.float32(0.424)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': '5. 6', 'start': 24, 'end': 27, 'score': np.float32(0.911)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##ccur', 'start': 30, 'end': 34, 'score': np.float32(0.428)}, {'entity': 'DATE_TIME', 'word': '06112023, 16 : 16 : 40 IST', 'start': 41, 'end': 63, 'score': np.float32(0.934)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Lat', 'start': 65, 'end': 68, 'score': np.float32(0.531)}, {'entity': 'DATE_TIME', 'word': ': 28. 89', 'start': 68, 'end': 75, 'score': np.float32(0.73)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': 'Long', 'start': 77, 'end': 81, 'score': np.float32(0.504)}, {'entity': 'DATE_TIME', 'word': ':', 'start': 81, 'end': 82, 'score': np.float32(0.368)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': '82. 36,', 'start': 83, 'end': 89, 'score': np.float32(0.634)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'De', 'start': 90, 'end': 92, 'score': np.float32(0.305)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': '##pth', 'start': 92, 'end': 95, 'score': np.float32(0.295)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': ':', 'start': 95, 'end': 96, 'score': np.float32(0.227)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': '10 Km', 'start': 97, 'end': 102, 'score': np.float32(0.933)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': 'Region', 'start': 104, 'end': 110, 'score': np.float32(0.169)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': ':', 'start': 110, 'end': 111, 'score': np.float32(0.157)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Nepal', 'start': 112, 'end': 117, 'score': np.float32(0.712)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Tremores', 'start': 118, 'end': 126, 'score': np.float32(0.692)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'north', 'start': 145, 'end': 150, 'score': np.float32(0.853)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'india', 'start': 151, 'end': 156, 'score': np.float32(0.793)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquakes', 'start': 157, 'end': 168, 'score': np.float32(0.988)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 169, 'end': 174, 'score': np.float32(0.64)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': '##NCR', 'start': 174, 'end': 177, 'score': np.float32(0.819)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'delhi', 'start': 178, 'end': 183, 'score': np.float32(0.611)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##earthquake', 'start': 183, 'end': 193, 'score': np.float32(0.769)}]"
WATCH: Earthquake measuring 5.6 magnitude jolts Nepal; tremors felt in DelhiNCR Earthquake DelhiEarthquake Nepal NepalEarthquake DelhiNCR,"[{'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'WATCH', 'start': 0, 'end': 5, 'score': np.float32(0.94)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Earthquake', 'start': 7, 'end': 17, 'score': np.float32(0.99)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': '5. 6 magnitude jolt', 'start': 28, 'end': 46, 'score': np.float32(0.891)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Nepal', 'start': 48, 'end': 53, 'score': np.float32(0.841)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'DelhiNCR', 'start': 71, 'end': 79, 'score': np.float32(0.737)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Earthquake', 'start': 80, 'end': 90, 'score': np.float32(0.978)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 91, 'end': 96, 'score': np.float32(0.897)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': '##E', 'start': 96, 'end': 97, 'score': np.float32(0.203)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##arthquake', 'start': 97, 'end': 106, 'score': np.float32(0.728)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Nepal', 'start': 107, 'end': 112, 'score': np.float32(0.462)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Nepal', 'start': 113, 'end': 118, 'score': np.float32(0.692)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##Earthquake', 'start': 118, 'end': 128, 'score': np.float32(0.666)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'DelhiNCR', 'start': 129, 'end': 137, 'score': np.float32(0.757)}]"
"Man, these frequent earthquakes in Delhi are really alarming, May Allah keep everyone safe. delhiearthquake","[{'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquakes', 'start': 20, 'end': 31, 'score': np.float32(0.993)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 35, 'end': 40, 'score': np.float32(0.995)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'Allah', 'start': 66, 'end': 71, 'score': np.float32(0.361)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'delhi', 'start': 92, 'end': 97, 'score': np.float32(0.731)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##ear', 'start': 97, 'end': 100, 'score': np.float32(0.71)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': '##th', 'start': 100, 'end': 102, 'score': np.float32(0.484)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##quake', 'start': 102, 'end': 107, 'score': np.float32(0.813)}]"
BreakingNews  Strong earthquake tremors felt in Delhi... Earthquake DelhiEarthquake tremors DelhiNCR News18JKLH,"[{'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'BreakingNews', 'start': 0, 'end': 12, 'score': np.float32(0.925)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquake', 'start': 21, 'end': 31, 'score': np.float32(0.997)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 48, 'end': 53, 'score': np.float32(0.995)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Earthquake', 'start': 57, 'end': 67, 'score': np.float32(0.988)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 68, 'end': 73, 'score': np.float32(0.933)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': '##E', 'start': 73, 'end': 74, 'score': np.float32(0.242)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##arthquake', 'start': 74, 'end': 83, 'score': np.float32(0.844)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 92, 'end': 97, 'score': np.float32(0.655)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': '##NCR News', 'start': 97, 'end': 105, 'score': np.float32(0.893)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': '##18', 'start': 105, 'end': 107, 'score': np.float32(0.764)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': '##JKLH', 'start': 107, 'end': 111, 'score': np.float32(0.88)}]"
Earthquake again? delhiearthquake,"[{'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Earthquake', 'start': 0, 'end': 10, 'score': np.float32(0.892)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'delhiearthquake', 'start': 18, 'end': 33, 'score': np.float32(0.502)}]"
Minor Earthquake Of 2.6 Magnitude Jolts Delhi Ahead Of Diwali earthquakedelhi DelhiNCR delhiearthquake Earthquake ABPLive,"[{'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Earthquake', 'start': 6, 'end': 16, 'score': np.float32(0.976)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': '2. 6 Magnitude', 'start': 20, 'end': 33, 'score': np.float32(0.868)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Jolts', 'start': 34, 'end': 39, 'score': np.float32(0.645)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 40, 'end': 45, 'score': np.float32(0.708)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Ahead Of', 'start': 46, 'end': 54, 'score': np.float32(0.37)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Diwali', 'start': 55, 'end': 61, 'score': np.float32(0.875)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquake', 'start': 62, 'end': 72, 'score': np.float32(0.854)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': '##delhi', 'start': 72, 'end': 77, 'score': np.float32(0.753)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 78, 'end': 83, 'score': np.float32(0.623)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': '##NCR', 'start': 83, 'end': 86, 'score': np.float32(0.948)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'delhi', 'start': 87, 'end': 92, 'score': np.float32(0.885)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##ear', 'start': 92, 'end': 95, 'score': np.float32(0.389)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': '##th', 'start': 95, 'end': 97, 'score': np.float32(0.556)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##quake', 'start': 97, 'end': 102, 'score': np.float32(0.872)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Earthquake', 'start': 103, 'end': 113, 'score': np.float32(0.972)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'ABPLive', 'start': 114, 'end': 121, 'score': np.float32(0.854)}]"
"Earthquake of Magnitude:5.6, Occurred on 06112023, 16:16:40 IST, Lat: 28.89  Long: 82.36, Depth: 10 Km ,Region: Nepal Tremores feels in parts of north india earthquakes DelhiNCR delhiearthquake Delhi earthquake","[{'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Earthquake', 'start': 0, 'end': 10, 'score': np.float32(0.989)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Magnitude', 'start': 14, 'end': 23, 'score': np.float32(0.403)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': '5. 6', 'start': 24, 'end': 27, 'score': np.float32(0.916)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##ccur', 'start': 30, 'end': 34, 'score': np.float32(0.409)}, {'entity': 'DATE_TIME', 'word': '06112023, 16 : 16 : 40 IST', 'start': 41, 'end': 63, 'score': np.float32(0.933)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Lat', 'start': 65, 'end': 68, 'score': np.float32(0.61)}, {'entity': 'DATE_TIME', 'word': ': 28. 89', 'start': 68, 'end': 75, 'score': np.float32(0.739)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': 'Long', 'start': 77, 'end': 81, 'score': np.float32(0.503)}, {'entity': 'DATE_TIME', 'word': ':', 'start': 81, 'end': 82, 'score': np.float32(0.381)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': '82. 36,', 'start': 83, 'end': 89, 'score': np.float32(0.63)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'De', 'start': 90, 'end': 92, 'score': np.float32(0.303)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': '##pth', 'start': 92, 'end': 95, 'score': np.float32(0.301)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': ':', 'start': 95, 'end': 96, 'score': np.float32(0.219)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': '10 Km', 'start': 97, 'end': 102, 'score': np.float32(0.932)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': 'Region', 'start': 104, 'end': 110, 'score': np.float32(0.173)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': ':', 'start': 110, 'end': 111, 'score': np.float32(0.15)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Nepal', 'start': 112, 'end': 117, 'score': np.float32(0.718)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Tremores', 'start': 118, 'end': 126, 'score': np.float32(0.685)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'north', 'start': 145, 'end': 150, 'score': np.float32(0.861)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'india', 'start': 151, 'end': 156, 'score': np.float32(0.802)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquakes', 'start': 157, 'end': 168, 'score': np.float32(0.986)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 169, 'end': 174, 'score': np.float32(0.484)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': '##NCR', 'start': 174, 'end': 177, 'score': np.float32(0.762)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'del', 'start': 178, 'end': 181, 'score': np.float32(0.523)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': '##hi', 'start': 181, 'end': 183, 'score': np.float32(0.391)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##earthquake', 'start': 183, 'end': 193, 'score': np.float32(0.786)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 194, 'end': 199, 'score': np.float32(0.934)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquake', 'start': 200, 'end': 210, 'score': np.float32(0.881)}]"
         ! . . . DelhiEarthquake Earthquake DelhiNCR Bhukamp EarthquakeInDelhi EarthquakeInDelhiNCR,"[{'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': '!', 'start': 9, 'end': 10, 'score': np.float32(0.287)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '.', 'start': 11, 'end': 12, 'score': np.float32(0.166)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'DelhiEarth', 'start': 17, 'end': 27, 'score': np.float32(0.732)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##quake', 'start': 27, 'end': 32, 'score': np.float32(0.795)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Earthquake', 'start': 33, 'end': 43, 'score': np.float32(0.955)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'DelhiNCR', 'start': 44, 'end': 52, 'score': np.float32(0.696)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Bhukamp', 'start': 53, 'end': 60, 'score': np.float32(0.994)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Earthquake', 'start': 61, 'end': 71, 'score': np.float32(0.953)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': '##I', 'start': 71, 'end': 72, 'score': np.float32(0.268)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##n', 'start': 72, 'end': 73, 'score': np.float32(0.33)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': '##Delhi', 'start': 73, 'end': 78, 'score': np.float32(0.838)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Earthquake', 'start': 79, 'end': 89, 'score': np.float32(0.948)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': '##I', 'start': 89, 'end': 90, 'score': np.float32(0.293)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##n', 'start': 90, 'end': 91, 'score': np.float32(0.39)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': '##Delhi', 'start': 91, 'end': 96, 'score': np.float32(0.759)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': '##NC', 'start': 96, 'end': 98, 'score': np.float32(0.368)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': '##R', 'start': 98, 'end': 99, 'score': np.float32(0.591)}]"
"Earthquake again in DelhiNCR Delhi ncr earthquakes earthquake earthquake earthquakenepal Nepal earthquakedelhi earthquakes Delhi NepalEarthquake Nepal Earthquakes DelhiNCR HeavyRain Israel delhiearthquake viralvideo DelhiAirQuality, DelhiPollution","[{'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Earthquake', 'start': 0, 'end': 10, 'score': np.float32(0.986)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 20, 'end': 25, 'score': np.float32(0.974)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': '##NCR', 'start': 25, 'end': 28, 'score': np.float32(0.686)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 29, 'end': 34, 'score': np.float32(0.87)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'n', 'start': 35, 'end': 36, 'score': np.float32(0.195)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##cr', 'start': 36, 'end': 38, 'score': np.float32(0.365)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquakes', 'start': 39, 'end': 50, 'score': np.float32(0.934)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquake', 'start': 51, 'end': 61, 'score': np.float32(0.959)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquake', 'start': 62, 'end': 72, 'score': np.float32(0.942)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquakenepal', 'start': 73, 'end': 88, 'score': np.float32(0.66)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Nepal', 'start': 89, 'end': 94, 'score': np.float32(0.528)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquake', 'start': 95, 'end': 105, 'score': np.float32(0.911)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': '##delhi', 'start': 105, 'end': 110, 'score': np.float32(0.626)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquakes', 'start': 111, 'end': 122, 'score': np.float32(0.886)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi Nepal', 'start': 123, 'end': 134, 'score': np.float32(0.709)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': '##E', 'start': 134, 'end': 135, 'score': np.float32(0.257)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##arthquake', 'start': 135, 'end': 144, 'score': np.float32(0.695)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'Nepal', 'start': 145, 'end': 150, 'score': np.float32(0.438)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Earthquakes', 'start': 151, 'end': 162, 'score': np.float32(0.937)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 163, 'end': 168, 'score': np.float32(0.518)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': '##NCR', 'start': 168, 'end': 171, 'score': np.float32(0.704)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'HeavyRain Israel', 'start': 172, 'end': 188, 'score': np.float32(0.7)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'delhi', 'start': 189, 'end': 194, 'score': np.float32(0.379)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##earthquake', 'start': 194, 'end': 204, 'score': np.float32(0.629)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'viralvideo', 'start': 205, 'end': 215, 'score': np.float32(0.681)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'DelhiAirQuality', 'start': 216, 'end': 231, 'score': np.float32(0.82)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': ',', 'start': 231, 'end': 232, 'score': np.float32(0.215)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 233, 'end': 238, 'score': np.float32(0.767)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': '##Pollution', 'start': 238, 'end': 247, 'score': np.float32(0.682)}]"
Another aftershock of Mag 5. Milder ones will continue for a while. Earthquake DelhiEarthquake,"[{'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'aftershock', 'start': 8, 'end': 18, 'score': np.float32(0.842)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Ma', 'start': 22, 'end': 24, 'score': np.float32(0.369)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##g 5', 'start': 24, 'end': 27, 'score': np.float32(0.827)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Milder', 'start': 29, 'end': 35, 'score': np.float32(0.803)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Earthquake', 'start': 68, 'end': 78, 'score': np.float32(0.978)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 79, 'end': 84, 'score': np.float32(0.677)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##Earthquake', 'start': 84, 'end': 94, 'score': np.float32(0.766)}]"
"Earthquake preliminary report: Magnitude: 6.4 Time: 23:32:54 IST Depth: 10 Km Epicenter Nepal Lat: 28.84  Long: 82.19 Strong tremors felt across Delhi NCR, UttarPradesh Bihar Haryana Uttarakhand Aftershocks might follow.","[{'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Earthquake', 'start': 0, 'end': 10, 'score': np.float32(0.991)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Magnitude', 'start': 31, 'end': 40, 'score': np.float32(0.654)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': '6. 4', 'start': 42, 'end': 45, 'score': np.float32(0.962)}, {'entity': 'DATE_TIME', 'word': 'Time', 'start': 46, 'end': 50, 'score': np.float32(0.49)}, {'entity': 'DATE_TIME', 'word': '23 : 32 : 54', 'start': 52, 'end': 60, 'score': np.float32(0.893)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'IS', 'start': 61, 'end': 63, 'score': np.float32(0.335)}, {'entity': 'DATE_TIME', 'word': '##T', 'start': 63, 'end': 64, 'score': np.float32(0.727)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Depth :', 'start': 65, 'end': 71, 'score': np.float32(0.391)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': '10 Km', 'start': 72, 'end': 77, 'score': np.float32(0.951)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Epicenter', 'start': 78, 'end': 87, 'score': np.float32(0.964)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Nepal', 'start': 88, 'end': 93, 'score': np.float32(0.804)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': 'La', 'start': 94, 'end': 96, 'score': np.float32(0.174)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': '##t', 'start': 96, 'end': 97, 'score': np.float32(0.442)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': ':', 'start': 97, 'end': 98, 'score': np.float32(0.234)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': '28', 'start': 99, 'end': 101, 'score': np.float32(0.597)}, {'entity': 'DATE_TIME', 'word': '.', 'start': 101, 'end': 102, 'score': np.float32(0.472)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': '84', 'start': 102, 'end': 104, 'score': np.float32(0.513)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Long', 'start': 106, 'end': 110, 'score': np.float32(0.28)}, {'entity': 'DATE_TIME', 'word': ':', 'start': 110, 'end': 111, 'score': np.float32(0.394)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': '82. 19', 'start': 112, 'end': 117, 'score': np.float32(0.639)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi NCR', 'start': 145, 'end': 154, 'score': np.float32(0.987)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'UttarPradesh Bihar Haryana Uttarakhand', 'start': 156, 'end': 194, 'score': np.float32(0.951)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##sh', 'start': 200, 'end': 202, 'score': np.float32(0.511)}]"
"Another earthquake in Nepal  felt close to Delhi USGS reports: M 5.6  42 km S of Jumla 28.888N 82.195E, Nepal at 17.9 km depth NCS India reports: M: 6.4  28.84, 82.19 at depth of 10km Data: USGS, Map prepared by me","[{'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquake', 'start': 8, 'end': 18, 'score': np.float32(0.997)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Nepal', 'start': 22, 'end': 27, 'score': np.float32(0.994)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 43, 'end': 48, 'score': np.float32(0.983)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'USGS', 'start': 49, 'end': 53, 'score': np.float32(0.991)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': '5. 6 42 km S', 'start': 65, 'end': 77, 'score': np.float32(0.854)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Jumla', 'start': 81, 'end': 86, 'score': np.float32(0.997)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': '28', 'start': 87, 'end': 89, 'score': np.float32(0.582)}, {'entity': 'DATE_TIME', 'word': '. 888N 82. 195', 'start': 89, 'end': 101, 'score': np.float32(0.66)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': '##E', 'start': 101, 'end': 102, 'score': np.float32(0.809)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Nepal', 'start': 104, 'end': 109, 'score': np.float32(0.971)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': '17. 9 km depth', 'start': 113, 'end': 126, 'score': np.float32(0.922)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'NCS India', 'start': 127, 'end': 136, 'score': np.float32(0.848)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': 'M :', 'start': 146, 'end': 148, 'score': np.float32(0.424)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': '6. 4', 'start': 149, 'end': 152, 'score': np.float32(0.625)}, {'entity': 'DATE_TIME', 'word': '28. 84,', 'start': 154, 'end': 160, 'score': np.float32(0.569)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': '82. 19 at depth', 'start': 161, 'end': 175, 'score': np.float32(0.61)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': '10km', 'start': 179, 'end': 183, 'score': np.float32(0.908)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'USGS', 'start': 190, 'end': 194, 'score': np.float32(0.993)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'me', 'start': 212, 'end': 214, 'score': np.float32(0.972)}]"
"M6.4 on Richter scale, M5.6 on Mw scale. Definitely much deadlier than the last one in oct","[{'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'M', 'start': 0, 'end': 1, 'score': np.float32(0.253)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': '##6. 4 on', 'start': 1, 'end': 7, 'score': np.float32(0.747)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Richter', 'start': 8, 'end': 15, 'score': np.float32(0.694)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': 'scale', 'start': 16, 'end': 21, 'score': np.float32(0.812)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'M', 'start': 23, 'end': 24, 'score': np.float32(0.328)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': '##5. 6 on Mw scale', 'start': 24, 'end': 39, 'score': np.float32(0.783)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'dead', 'start': 57, 'end': 61, 'score': np.float32(0.697)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': 'oct', 'start': 87, 'end': 90, 'score': np.float32(0.375)}]"
Nothing strong it was minor very minor tremors felt,[]
Pretty similar to one in 2015 Nepal quake I think ..lets hope everyone is safe...,"[{'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Nepal', 'start': 30, 'end': 35, 'score': np.float32(0.452)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'quake', 'start': 36, 'end': 41, 'score': np.float32(0.918)}]"
It is getting stronger and stronger day by day Stay safe,"[{'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'stronger', 'start': 27, 'end': 35, 'score': np.float32(0.238)}, {'entity': 'DATE_TIME', 'word': 'day', 'start': 43, 'end': 46, 'score': np.float32(0.221)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Stay safe', 'start': 47, 'end': 56, 'score': np.float32(0.173)}]"
Felt it... as if the floor lifted under my chair a bit!,"[{'entity': 'DATE_TIME', 'word': '.', 'start': 7, 'end': 8, 'score': np.float32(0.223)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': '.', 'start': 8, 'end': 9, 'score': np.float32(0.158)}, {'entity': 'DATE_TIME', 'word': '.', 'start': 9, 'end': 10, 'score': np.float32(0.211)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'floor', 'start': 21, 'end': 26, 'score': np.float32(0.302)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'chair', 'start': 43, 'end': 48, 'score': np.float32(0.167)}]"
"Earthquake of Magnitude:5.6, Occurred on 06112023, 16:16:40 IST, Lat: 28.89  Long: 82.36, Depth: 10 Km ,Region: Nepal Tremores feels in parts of north india earthquakes DelhiNCR delhiearthquake","[{'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Earthquake', 'start': 0, 'end': 10, 'score': np.float32(0.989)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Magnitude', 'start': 14, 'end': 23, 'score': np.float32(0.424)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': '5. 6', 'start': 24, 'end': 27, 'score': np.float32(0.911)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##ccur', 'start': 30, 'end': 34, 'score': np.float32(0.428)}, {'entity': 'DATE_TIME', 'word': '06112023, 16 : 16 : 40 IST', 'start': 41, 'end': 63, 'score': np.float32(0.934)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Lat', 'start': 65, 'end': 68, 'score': np.float32(0.531)}, {'entity': 'DATE_TIME', 'word': ': 28. 89', 'start': 68, 'end': 75, 'score': np.float32(0.73)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': 'Long', 'start': 77, 'end': 81, 'score': np.float32(0.504)}, {'entity': 'DATE_TIME', 'word': ':', 'start': 81, 'end': 82, 'score': np.float32(0.368)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': '82. 36,', 'start': 83, 'end': 89, 'score': np.float32(0.634)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'De', 'start': 90, 'end': 92, 'score': np.float32(0.305)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': '##pth', 'start': 92, 'end': 95, 'score': np.float32(0.295)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': ':', 'start': 95, 'end': 96, 'score': np.float32(0.227)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': '10 Km', 'start': 97, 'end': 102, 'score': np.float32(0.933)}, {'entity': 'MAGNITUDE', 'word': 'Region', 'start': 104, 'end': 110, 'score': np.float32(0.169)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': ':', 'start': 110, 'end': 111, 'score': np.float32(0.157)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Nepal', 'start': 112, 'end': 117, 'score': np.float32(0.712)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'Tremores', 'start': 118, 'end': 126, 'score': np.float32(0.692)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'north', 'start': 145, 'end': 150, 'score': np.float32(0.853)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'india', 'start': 151, 'end': 156, 'score': np.float32(0.793)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquakes', 'start': 157, 'end': 168, 'score': np.float32(0.988)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 169, 'end': 174, 'score': np.float32(0.64)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': '##NCR', 'start': 174, 'end': 177, 'score': np.float32(0.819)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'delhi', 'start': 178, 'end': 183, 'score': np.float32(0.611)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##earthquake', 'start': 183, 'end': 193, 'score': np.float32(0.769)}]"
earthquake in DelhiNCR where people are already suffering from Bad AQI. Delhiearthquake DelhiAirPollution DelhiAirQuality DelhiNCR DelhiInGasChamber,"[{'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'earthquake', 'start': 0, 'end': 10, 'score': np.float32(0.985)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'DelhiNCR', 'start': 14, 'end': 22, 'score': np.float32(0.821)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': 'AQI', 'start': 67, 'end': 70, 'score': np.float32(0.694)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 72, 'end': 77, 'score': np.float32(0.916)}, {'entity': 'DISASTER_TYPE', 'word': '##earthquake', 'start': 77, 'end': 87, 'score': np.float32(0.699)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'DelhiAirPollution', 'start': 88, 'end': 105, 'score': np.float32(0.643)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': 'DelhiAirQuality', 'start': 106, 'end': 121, 'score': np.float32(0.778)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'DelhiNCR', 'start': 122, 'end': 130, 'score': np.float32(0.579)}, {'entity': 'LOCATION', 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 131, 'end': 136, 'score': np.float32(0.899)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': '##In', 'start': 136, 'end': 138, 'score': np.float32(0.561)}, {'entity': 'ORGANIZATION', 'word': '##GasChamber', 'start': 138, 'end': 148, 'score': np.float32(0.502)}]"
